Guide to the The Review of Contemporary Fiction/Dalkey Archive Press: records, 1980-1990
Department of Special Collections
- Series II: Dalkey Archive Press
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence: Tindall 1981, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Tindall 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Tindall (Sept. 11, 1986 and 2 copies of Rev. Ruggles' sermon); Photographs (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Tindall 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Clippings: Tindall (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - All the Flowers - Kenneth Tindall (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - -Athena Noctua - From a novel in progress- Kenneth Tindall (pp. 1-14) (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - -Pignon - From a novel in progress - Kenneth Tindall (pp. 1-21) (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Pigeon - Kenneth Tindall (dedicated): title page-p. 65 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Pigeon: (pp. 66-127) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Banks of the Sea - Kenneth Tindall (title page pp. 73) version 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Banks of the Sea - Kenneth Tindall: (pp. 74-142) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 143-192) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 193-234) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 3-70) version 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp.71-137) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 138-214) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 143-192) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 193-234) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 3-70) version 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 71-137) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (pp. 138-214) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (corrections of Galley) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (Galley pp. 1-69) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (Galley pp. 70-136) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - The Banks of the Sea: (Galley pp. 137-184) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Doug Woolf and Ed Dorn re: Wall to Wall (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Impossible Object - Nicholas Mosley (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Some Instructions - Stanley Crawford (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Accident - Nicholas Mosley (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Cadenza: An Excursion - Ralph Cusack (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and corrections: Alan Ansen (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Moore (re: Ansen) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Moore/Ansen (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Index of Titles (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 - Alan Ansen (pp. I-XXXIV) (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 (pp. 1-59) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 (pp. 60-113) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 (pp. 114-167) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 (pp. 168-210) (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Contents (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Introduction (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Introduction 3rd draft (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Introduction 2nd draft (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Introduction let draft (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Ansen Time-line Biography (handwritten) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Ansen Introduction: handwritten copy and addenda to Introduction and copy editor comments (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 - Alan Ansen (Text Copy, pp. 1-49) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 - Alan Ansen (Text Copy I pp. 50-99) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - -Contact Highs: Selected Poems 1957-1987 - Alan Ansen (Text Copy pp. 100-152) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Compact: Introduction, notes of the translation, corrections, correspondence (Mark Polizzotti) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - -Compact: a Novel - Maurice Roche (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Compact: - Maurice Roche (pp. 1-65) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Compact: - Maurice Roche (pp. 66-133) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Part One - -Murder at Sainte-Gudule and two drawings-Jacques Roubaud (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Part Two - -The Poldevian Connection (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Part Three - -Passion (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Part Four - -Escape (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Part Five - -The Abduction (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Part Six - -Carlotta versus K'manoroigs and Epilogue (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Part One - -Murder at Sainte-Gudule (edited version) and letter - Jacques Roubaud (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Part Two - -The Poldevian Connection (edited version) (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Part Three - -Passion (edited version) (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Part Four - -Escape (edited version) (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Part Five - -The Abduction (edited version) (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Part Six - -Carlotta versus Kinanoroigs (edited version) (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - -Excerpts From the Secret Notebooks of the Author...-Jacques Roubaud (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - -Mordechai Schamz (Far From God II) - Marc Cholondenko (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - -Mordechai Schamz - Marc Cholodenko (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - -Mordechai Schamz - Marc Cholodenko (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Alfau
    - Correspondence: Moore (re: Alfau) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Alfau/Locos (Jacket description) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Locos - Alfau (Prologue and pp. 1-98 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Locos - Alfau (pp. 99-206) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Locos - Alfau (excerpts) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - -Thcms Pynchon: A Bibliography of Primary and Secondary Materials - Clifford Mead (pp. 1-94) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - -Thcms Pynchon: A Bibliography of Primary and Secondary Materials - Clifford Mead(pp. 95-end) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - -The Dalkey Archive Bibliography Series-Thomas Pynchon (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - -Thomas Pyncbon: A Bibliography of Primary and Secondary Materials - Clifford Head (letter, advertisenent, and pagination plan) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - -The New York Review of Books (contains Mccarthy' s afterward to Locos) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 1-105) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 106-211) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 1-105) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 106-212) (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sections of Street Girl (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 1-94) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Street Girl - Muriel Cerf (pp. 95-199) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Imago Bird (pp. 1-96) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Imago Bird (pp. 97-186) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Imago Bird (N.T.Y.?? - From box 12 (4)) (pp. 1-96) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Imago Bird (N.T.Y.?? - From box 12 (4)) (pp. 97-186) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Roubaud
    - Correspondence (re: Roubaud) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - -Something Black - Jacques Roubaud (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - -Something Black - Jacques Roubaud (proofs-copies) (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Serpent - Nicholas Mosley (advanced uncorrected galley, pp. 1-88) (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Serpent - Nicholas Mosley, pp. 89-192) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Something Black - Jacques Roubaud. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Something Black - Jacques Roubaud. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Serpent - Nicholas Mosley (pp. 1-96) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Serpent - Nicholas Mosley (pp. 97-192) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Banks of the Sea -Kenneth Tindail (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Banks of the Sea -Kenneth Tindail (pp.97-214) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Sorrentino
    - Cover design for Misterioso and Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp. 1-83) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp. (Box 16, Folder 9)
      84-167)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp. (Box 16, Folder 10)
      168-256)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp.257-340) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino: printed copy (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino: final draft (pp. 1-82) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino: final draft(pp. 83-181) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Misterioso - Gilbert Sorrentino: final draft(pp. 182-282) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Misteriso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp. 1-82) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Misteriso - Gilbert Sorrentino(pp. 83-181) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Misteriso - Gilbert Sorrentino (pp. 182-282) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Disconnection - Claude Ollier (pp. 1-85) (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Disconnection - Claude Ollier (pp. 86-163) (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Disconnection - Claude Ollier:Notes by the translator and galleys (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Disconnection - Claude Ollier (jacket copy and review) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Disconnection - Claude Ollier (pp. 1-89 incomplete) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Sections From Disconnection - Claude Ollier (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Catastrophe Practice - -Introduction - Banks (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - -Introduction to Catastrophe Practice - Banks (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Catastrophe Practice - -Skylight - Mosley (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - catastrophe Practice - -Landfall - Mosley (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - catastrophe Practice -Cell - Mosley (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - catastrophe Practice -Cypher - Mosiey (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Postscript 1988 to Catastrophe Practice (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - catastrophe Practice - -Introduction and -Skylight (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - catastrophe Practice -Landfall (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - catastrophe Practice -Cell (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - catastrophe Practice -Cypher (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Catastrophe Practice - -Introduction and -Skylight (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - catastrophe Practice -Landfall (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - catastrophe Practice -cell (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - catastrophe Practice "Cypher" (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - catastrophe Practice -Postscript (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: rejected proposals (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: rejected proposals (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Moore - Sullivan (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - The Dead Magician - Evelin Sullivan (Advance Uncorrected Galley) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Journey to Weilsend - E.E. Van (pp. 1-85) (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Journey to Weilsend - E.E. Van (pp. 86-190) (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Journey to Weilsend - E.E. Van (pp. 191-268) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Journey to Weilsend - E.E. Van (pp. 269-343) (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Journey to Welisend: Part One - E.E. Van (pp. 344-431) (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Journey to Welisend: Part One - E.E. Van (pp. 432-498) (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Journey to Welisend: Part One - E.E. Van (pp. 499-560) (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - The Dead Magician - E.E. Sullivan (proofread galleys and list of corrections, pp. 1-94) (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - The Dead Magician - E.E. Sullivan (proofread galleys, pp. 95-200) (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - The Dead Magician - E.E. Sullivan (proofread galleys, pp. 201-316) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (Moore's correction, pp. 1-111,incomplete) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (Moore's correction,(pp. 89-194) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (Moore's correction, (pp. 195-275) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (Moore's correction, (pp. 276-347) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (Biographical statement, jacket description and Introduction) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (pp. 21-88) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (pp. 89-194) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (pp. 195-275) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (pp. 276-347) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - The Dead Magician - E. E. Van (pp. 348-409) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Button - Moore (re: Dahlberg)
    - Samuel Beckett's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Various articles pertaining to Dalhberg and his works (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Dalhberg (jacket copy and copyright) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Dahlberg (Index) (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp. 1-74) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp.75-144) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp.1-83) (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp.84-159) (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp.160-240) (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Samuel Beckett 's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose -Edward Dahlberg (pp.241-323) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Markson
    - Correspondence: (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Moore - Markson
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress -David Markson (Advance Uncorrected Galley) (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress -David Markson (Jacket copy, front matter) (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress -David Markson (first proofs, pp.7-79) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress -David Markson (first proofs, pp. 80-159) (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Wittgenstein's Mistress -David Markson (first proofs, pp. 160-240) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Wittgenstein' Mistress -David Markson (final revision, pp. 1-90) (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Wittgenstein' Mistress -David Markson (final revision, pp. 91-190) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Wittgenstein' Mistress -David Markson (final revision, pp. 191-284) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Keeper of the Ghosts (same as Wittqenstein's Mistress) David Markson (first version, pp. 1-90) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Keeper of the Ghosts (same as Wittqenstein's Mistress) David Markson (first version, pp. 91-190) (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Keeper of the Ghosts (same as Wittqenstein's Mistress) David Markson (first version, pp. 191-284) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Queneau
    - Odile - Rayncnd Queneau (Introduction and pp. 1-61) (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Odile - Rayncnd Queneau (pp. 62-127) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Odile - Rayncnd Queneau (entire text) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Odile - Rayncnd Queneau (entire text) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Latin American Writers
    - Interviews with Latin American Writers - Introduction (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Interview: Isabel Allende (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Interview: Guillermo Cabrera Infante (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Interview: Jose Donoso (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Interview: Rosario Ferre (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Interview: Carlos Fuentes (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Interview: Isaac Goldenberg (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Interview: Juan Carlos Onetti (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Interview: Nicanor Parra (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Interview: Elena Poniatowska (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Interview: Manuel Puig (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Interview: Ernesto Sabato (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Interview: Luis Rafael Sanchez (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Interview: Severo Sarduy (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Interview: Luisa Valenzuela (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Interview: Mario Vargas Liosa (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Selected Bibliography (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Contents; Introduction (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Works in fl)~llsh Thanslation (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Advance Uncorrected Galleys: (Box 26)
      20 Lines a Day - Henry Mathews; Chromos - Felipe Alfau; LOCOS: A Comedy of Gestures - Felipe Alfau; Street Girl - Muriel Cerf; Mordechai Scbainz - Marc Cholodenko; Where Do You Put the Horse? - Paul Metcalf; Catastrophe Practice - Nicholas Mosley; Imago Bird - Nichoas Mosley; Serpent - Nicholas Mosley; Our Share of Time - Yves Navarre; Disconnection - Claude Ollier; The Mise-en-Scene - Claude Ollier; Odile - Raynxnd Queneau; Compact - Maurice Roche; Hortense Is Abducted - Jacques Roubaud; Some Thing Black - Jacques Roubaud; Theory of Prose - Viktor Shklovsky; Samuel Beckett's Wake and Other Uncollected Prose
- Series III: Black Writers Interviews
  - Colter, Cyrus (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Demby, William (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dodson, Owen (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ellison, Ralph (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gaines, Ernest (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harper, Michael (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hayden, Robert (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Major, Clarence (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marshall, Paule (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mayfield, Julian (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Petry, Ann (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Pharr, Robert Deane (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Reed, Ishamel (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Walker, Alice (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Wideman, John (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Williams, John A. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Young, Al (Box 1, Folder 17)